2joomla.net 2010-06-13

# Privacy Policy - 2Joomla.NET

#### Information about our Organization and Web site

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like 2JoomlaNet.

Our principal activity is: 

  * Development of web applications
  * Joomla extensions development

Our privacy policy covers 2JoomlaNet and its Web site.   

#### Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

#### Automatic Collection of Information

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.

#### Data Collection and Purpose Specification

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.  
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.  
We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.  
If we wish to use our visitors' personal data for new purposes, we do not give them the opportunity to consent to those new purposes.

#### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.  
We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.  
We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.

#### Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.

#### Confidentiality / Security

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data.  
We have not implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorized access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorized modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

Our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are not obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.  
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

#### Access to the personal data we may hold about you

You can ask us, by: 

  * sending an email ( [question@2joomla.net](mailto:question@2joomla.net) )
  * visiting this url ( [www.2joomla.net](http://www.2joomla.net/) )
  * calling this telephone number ( +380509701749 )

whether we are keeping personal data about you.  
We do not provide our visitors with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about them.  
We do not allow our visitors to challenge the data that we hold about them.  
We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.  
We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

#### Privacy Compliance

We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the privacy instrument.

#### Privacy Support

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:  
Email address  [question@2joomla.net](mailto:question@2joomla.net)  
URL    [www.2joomla.net](http://www.2joomla.net/)

We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed.
